behindthename.com 2019-12-02

# Privacy Policy - Behind the Name

_Last updated May 17, 2018._

Thank you for using BehindTheName.com! We are committed to protecting the privacy of our visitors. The following summarizes the information-gathering and dissemination practices for this website.

## Personal Information

BehindTheName.com requires that users enter a login name and email address when registering as a member. The email address is kept private. After registering for the member account, personal information may optionally be entered into the member's profile. You may also provide information when you post on the message boards, create online polls, submit names, or leave comments on names.

## IP Address

BehindTheName.com records user IP addresses to help administer this website. When a user posts content to the website, the user's IP address at the time of the posting may be recorded. If you post anonymously (meaning not signed in), this IP address may be displayed with the content.

## Cookies

If you sign in to this website and check the "remember me" box, BehindTheName.com creates a cookie on your computer to help us remember who you are each time you return to the website. Personal information is not stored in this cookie, nor is information about you from which your individual identity might be established.

## Information Sharing

BehindTheName.com does not share personal information (as described above) with third parties.

## Information Removal

You may edit your profile information or delete your member account by signing in and selecting the the "Edit Profile" menu option. Deleting your account does not delete any content you posted to BehindTheName.com while signed in to that account. To delete posted content, email [privacy@behindthename.com](mailto:privacy@behindthename.com).

## Third-Party Advertisers

BehindTheName.com uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit this website. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Some advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on this site. BehindTheName.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, these advertising partners.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, you may visit <https://www.aboutads.info/consumers> (United States), [https://www.youronlinechoices.com](https://www.youronlinechoices.com/) (Europe), <https://youradchoices.ca/> (Canada) or <http://www.youronlinechoices.com.au/> (Australia).
